Okay, pick a card.
Any card.
All right, now memorize it.
Show it to everybody.
Got it?
All right.
Give it back to me.
Five of hearts.
Real magic does exist.
Joey, how do you do it?
I can't tell you that.
Somebody's at the door on the ceiling.
That's our unbelievably loud
upstairs neighbor.
He took up the carpets,
and now you can hear everything.
Why don't you go ask him
to just, "Step lightly, please?"
I have, like five times.
But the guy is so charming...
... I go up there to yell,
then I end up apologizing to him.
That is silly!
I'll go up and tell him
to keep it down.
-All right, be my guest.
-Good luck.
All right, all right...
...if you wanna know how I did it,
I'll show you.
When you handed me back the card,
what you didn't see was...
... I looked at it so fast,
it was invisible to the naked eye.
I just did it.
Just did it again.
Here, I'll slow it down
so you guys can see it. Ready?
-I got it now!
-Okay.
Thank you.
The One Where Chandler
Can't Remember Which Sister
Anybody got a length of rope about
6 feet long, with a noose at the end?
-Honey, what's the matter?
-I just saw Janice.
She was at Rockefeller Center, skating
with her husband. She looked so happy.
I almost feel bad for whipping
that kid's pretzel at them.
I remember the first time I saw
Katherine after we broke up.
She was walking and talking
with her friend, Donna.
God, it killed me!
But you ended up having sex
with both of them that afternoon.
Sorry, I just
Any excuse to tell that story.
There's a party tomorrow.
You'll feel better then.
I'm gonna be okay. You don't
have to throw a party for me.
It's Joey's birthday.
Then if anybody should have a party,
it should be him.
I cannot believe
she's still up there.
Well, he totally
screwed up the punch line.
You know, it's supposed to be
How's that coffee coming, dear?
Right away, Mr. IKaplan.
I'm not suppose to drink it.
It makes me gassy.
I know.
I'll bet you're thinking,
"What's an intelligent girl...
...who wants to be in fashion
doing making coffee?"
You got me.
Don't think I haven't noticed
your potential.
I've got a project for you
that's a lot more related to fashion.
-How does that sound?
-That sounds great!
-Come on over here, sweetheart.
-Thank you so much.
I need these hangers separated
ASAP.
You're welcome.
Oh, God, I hate my job!
I hate it.
I know, honey. I'm sorry.
I want to quit, but then I think l
should stick it out.
Then I think:
"Why would a person stay
in such a demeaning job...
...just because it's remotely related
to the field they're interested in?
Gee, I don't know, Rach.
Order up! Yentl soup, James Beans,
and a Howdy, hold the Doody.
Come on, I'm sorry.
I didn't
I don't mind paying my dues.
But how much
will I learn about fashion...
... by walking Myra,
the arthritic seamstress...
...to the bathroom?
Hi.
Is my misery amusing to you?
I'm sorry, I was just....
It's not funny.
This is actually my job.
Believe me, I've been there.
I had to sort mannequin heads
at that Mannequins Plus.
I'm just gonna go back
to talking to my friend here.
You can go back to enjoying
your little hamburger.
Just one other thing.
I work at Bloomingdale's.
I might know of a possible job,
if you're interested.
Do you want my pickle?
Hey, guys.
-Hey, Gunther.
-Hi.
You're going on a date
with the noisy guy upstairs?
Well, he's very charming.
He's too charming!
But if you go out,
it'll be harder for me to hate him.
You'll just have to try.
Joey? Where are the Jell-O shots?
I don't know. Chandler's
supposed to be passing them
Chandler!
Hello-dee-lo!
Well, somebody's feeling better.
-Stick out your tongue!
-Take off your shirt!
-Oh, my!
-Oh, my God!
How many did you have?
They're pure vodka.
Yeah, Jell-O.
Just like Mom used to make.
The most unbelievable thing
happened today.
I had lunch at Monica's
and met a guy...
...who works for a buyer
at Bloomingdale's.
There's an opening there!
So I gave him my phone number...
...and he'll call me this weekend
to get me an interview!
So this guy's helping you
for no apparent reason?
And he's a total stranger?
Yeah. His name is "Mark" something.
Sounds like "Mark Something"
wants to have some sex!
What?
Why else would he swoop
in out of nowhere for no reason?
To be nice?
Hey, Joey, are men ever nice
to strange women for no reason?
-No, only for sex.
-Thank you.
So did you tell
"Mark Something" about me?
I didn't have to.
I was wearing...
... my "I Heart Ross" sandwich board
and ringing my bell.
Joey!
Happy birthday!
How many of that girl are you seeing?
How hammered are you?
These are Joey's sisters.
Hi, Joey's sisters!
What're we drinking over here?
Well, I have a vodka
and cranberry juice.
No kidding?
That's the same drink I made myself
right after I shot my husband.
Okay, I don't know how
to talk to you.
What are you doing?
I'm taking my ex-girlfriend
off my speed dialer.
No, it's a good thing.
Why must we dial so speedily anyway?
Why rush through life?
Why can't we savor
the precious moments?
You have some huge breasts!
-Hi.
So I heard about this Mark guy
that Rachel met today.
Isn't it great?
Yeah, pretty good.
He sounds like a nice, good guy.
Oh, he is.
And he is so dreamy!
I mean, when he left,
I actually used the phrase:
"Hummina, hummina, hummina."
That's excellent.
So he's "just a nice guy."
Do you really think this Mark
doesn't want anything for helping you?
Well, I assume I'll
have to take showers with him.
But that's true of any job.
How you feeling?
Well, my apartment isn't
there anymore...
... because I drank it.
Where'd you go? We lost you
after you opened up all the presents.
I ended up in the storage room,
and not alone.
No "woo-hooing." No "woo-hooing."
Why, what happened?
I fooled around with Joey's sister.
That's not the worst part.
What is the worst part?
I can't remember which sister.
You see what men do?
Don't tell me men are nice.
This is men!
Are you insane?
Joey will kill you.
He'll actually kill you dead.
You don't think I thought of that?
-How can you not know which one?
-That's unbelievable.
-Was it Gina?
-Which one's Gina?
The dark, big hair,
with airplane earrings.
That's Dina, not Gina.
See? You can't tell
which is which either!
We didn't fool around
with any of them.
It's got to be Veronica.
The girl in the red skirt.
I definitely stuck my tongue
down her throat!
That was me.
When I drink, sometimes
I get overly friendly...
-...and I'm sorry.
-That's okay.
-That's all right.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Hey, Joey!
Come on.
Why can't we talk in here...
...with witnesses?
I just got off the phone
with my sister.
Which one?
-Mary Angela.
Now which one is she again?
Ask Chandler.
He fooled around with her.
She told me you said
you could really fall for her.
Is that true, or are you just getting
over Janice by groping my sister?
It's gotta be the first one.
Really?
That's great!
You and my sister, sitting in a tree!
Yep, I'm in a tree.
Did he call? Did Mark call?
I'm sorry.
But the weekend's not over yet.
Oh, my God! Is that Phoebe?
Guess they're back from their date.
Music!
Very nice!
Oh, my God!
So how are you?
-I am good. I finished my book.
-What's it about?
I don't remember.
Do you want to take a walk?
"Dear Mary Angela:
Hi, how's it going?
This is the hardest letter
I've ever had to write."
What the hell's the matter with you?
How will Joey react to you
blowing off his sister with a letter?
That's where you tell him
that I moved to France...
...when actually I'll be in Cuba.
Look, you've got to do this
yourself in person.
You know her name.
You just go to the house
and ask for Mary Angela.
When whichever one she is
comes to the door...
...take her for a walk
and let her down easy.
What if she comes to the door
and I ask for her?
Where in Cuba?
What are you doing here?
Waiting for my grandma
to do my laundry.
What about you?
I'm here to see Mary Angela.
You are so the man! Come on.
Now look, listen.
Listen....
Be cool, because Grandma
doesn't know about you two.
You don't want to tick her off.
She was, like, the sixth person
to spit on Mussolini's hanging body.
Where's Mary Angela?
She's right in there.
-Hey, Chandler!
I can't believe Mark didn't call.
It's Sunday night and he didn't call.
Bummer.
Yeah, right. Look at you.
You're practically giddy.
I'm genuinely sorry
the Mark thing didn't work out.
Look, Rach, I want
only good things for you.
Wait a minute.
Why don't you just call Mark?
Who says you have to sit
and wait for him?
You've got to make stuff happen!
Yeah, but you don't
wanna seem too pushy.
It's not pushy.
He gave her his home number.
He gave you his home number,
as in, to his home?
And you don't mind if I call,
because you want good things for me.
That's right, good things.
That is what I said.
Mark? Hi, it's Rachel Greene.
Oh, no.
Don't you apologize.
Yeah, I'll hold.
He left my number at work.
Then he had to help his niece
with her report on the pioneers.
That is so made up!
Oh, my God! Tomorrow?
That's
No, it's perfect.
Oh, God!
Thank you so much!
Great.
I got the interview!
There you go!
He even offered to meet me for lunch
and prep me for it.
That is amazing!
Well, if I know Mark,
and I think I do...
...I'd expect nothing less.
I gotta figure out what to wear.
High collar and baggy pants say,
"I'm a pro!"
Yeah, right.
Okay, I'll see you guys later.
You go get them!
What did I do to you?
Did I hurt you in some way?
What?
"Why don't you call him?"
Thank you very much.
Now he's gonna prep her...
...as in what you do before
you surgically remove the boyfriend!
Are you crazy?
Am l? Am I out of my mind?
Am I losing my senses?
This dreamy guy's taking my girlfriend
out for a meal!
This isn't even about you!
It's about something wonderful
happening for Rachel.
Even if you're right,
and he wants to sleep with her...
...does that mean he gets to?
-No, but
-Don't you trust her?
Then get over yourself!
Grow up!
You grow up.
This tiramisu is excellent.
Did you make it, Mary Angela?
No, I did.
Well, it's yummy.
So....
Mary Angela, do you like it?
Of course.
It's her favorite.
So....
Mary Angela, what's
your second favorite?
More of Grandma's tiramisu.
Oh, would you just please...
...give me your recipe, because
this is great! It's topnotch!
That dies with me.
So will l.
Excuse yourself
and go to the bathroom.
I was just squinting.
It doesn't mean anything.
Just do it!
Will you excuse me, I have to....
Finally! I thought we'd
never be alone.
Can I just tell you something?
I have not stopped thinking about you
since the party.
Look, I may have jumped the gun here.
I just got out of a relationship.
And I'm not really in a...
...in a commitment kind of place.
So? Me neither!
God, Mary Angela was right.
You do have the softest lips.
You're not Mary Angela?
No! I'm Mary Therese!
This is so bad.
If you're not Mary Angela,
then who is?
I am.
Oh, it's so bad.
No, Joey! No, Joey!
What's going on?
You're it!
Now run and hide!
It's no big deal.
Chandler was just kissing me...
... because he thought
I was Mary Angela.
What? How could you
think she was Mary Angela?
I wasn't sure which one
Mary Angela was.
Look, I'm sorry.
I was really drunk...
...and you guys
all look really similar.
-I say punch him, Joey!
-Yeah, punch him!
We should all calm down...
... because your brother's
not gonna punch me.
Are you?
That's usually what I'd do.
But I never thought you'd be
on the receiving end.
How could you do this?
If you wanna punch me, go ahead.
I deserve it.
But I want you to know that I'd never
soberly hurt you or your family.
You're my best friend.
And I'd never do anything
like this, ever again.
So what?
-I say punch him!
-Yeah, punch him!
No, I'm not gonna punch Chandler.
-I'll do it.
-No, you won't!
He knows he did a terrible thing,
and I believe him. He's sorry.
But you got one more apology to make.
You gotta apologize to Mary Angela.
-Absolutely. You got it.
-All right.
-Cookie, now you can punch him!
-What?
What are you doing here?
You know, this building's
on my paper route, so....
How did it go?
The woman I interviewed with
was pretty tough...
... but thank God Mark coached me.
Once I talked about the Fall line,
she got all happy.
-I'm so proud of you.
-Me too!
Listen, I'm....
I'm sorry I've been
so crazy and jealous and....
It's just,
I like you a lot, so....
I know.
-Hi.
-Hi, Mark.
I just talked to Joanna,
and she loves you. You got the job.
I did?
Oh, my God!
Congratulations....
So, Phoebe?
How was your date?
Oh, well, you know....
Yeah, I do know.
You were eavesdropping?
Eavesdropping? Pheebs, the ceiling
tiles were falling down.
Oh, I'm sorry.
But I really like this guy
and I think he really likes me.
Maybe he's just...
...jumping on a pogo stick
and he really likes it.
Maybe the pogo stick likes it too.
All right, that's it.
He cannot do this to Phoebe!
This guy's gonna get
the butt-kicking of a lifetime!
But is he a big guy?
We'll all go. Come on.
Thanks, you guys.
Thank you!
Don't worry!
God!
I hope they kick his ass!
Honey, I'm sorry.
If it's any consolation...
...he sounded like
he had more fun with you.